lagunatools.com 2016-11-20

# Laguna Tools Privacy Policy

|   
  
| 

|  | ****  
---|---  
  
**Privacy Policy for Laguna Tools**

If you require any more information or have any additional questions about our privacy polcy, please don't hesitate to contact us by phone at 800-234-1976 or e-mail at mail@lagunatools.com.

At lagunatools.com we consider the privacy of our visitors to be very impotant. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information collected and recorded by lagunatools.com and how we use it.

Like many other Web sites, www.lagunatools.com makes use of log files. These files merely log visitors to the site – usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services’s analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

www.lagunatools.com uses cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

This website and its contents are protected under U.S. and international law as copyrighted works. Reproduction, display, copies or derivations of this work and/or sale of this work without the express written permission of Laguna Tools is expressly prohibited. Anyone who displays, reproduces, copies, creates derivative works for commercial or non-commercial purposes without the express written permission of Laguna Tools is in violation of copyright law and is liable for copyright infringement and all other penalties authorized by law including, but not limited to criminal prosecution. 17 U.S.C. Section 106.

Thank you for visiting the Laguna Tools website. Laguna Tools is a direct marketing company in the business of selling woodworking machinery and accessories.

Laguna Tools does not sell, rent or trade personal information collected about you to any other business entity. 

During your visit to Lagunatools.com we may ask you to provide us with such personal information as your e-mail, name, address and phone number. This information may be used by Laguna Tools to provide you with updated information on our products, special offers, company newsletters or any other information that we believe would be of interest to you. In the event that you would like to be removed from our mailing or e-mail list please contact us by phone at 800-234-1976 or e-mail at mail@lagunatools.com.
